hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jeremy
Krakowski and I help coaches mentors
trainers authors and speakers scale
their businesses to make 200 to 500 000
a year and Beyond in their business but
that's the starting point I want to get
everybody to that quarter of a million
half a million dollar level when they
work with me if you're listening to this
that's the goal I'm not trying to get
you to just make 500 to a thousand
dollars a month in your business I want
you to be able to make a full-time
income applying the strategies that I
teach you and that's why sometimes I'm
going to challenge your way of thinking
that's what this podcast does that's
what my virtual events do by the way we
have an event coming up here about
launching your six-figure group coaching
offer don't miss that check it out and
if you do miss that be sure to go to my
social media or my website at
jeremicorkowski.com we do events all the
time where I walk you through how to
actually create step by step a strategy
and a system that scales a coaching
business to multiple six figures
my wife and I we've brought in over a
half a million dollars in the last seven
months in our business and I want to
show you how you can do the exact same
as well I'm excited we're on track to a
seven figure income this year and this
is the best year in business this is the
most money I've ever made personally and
I can't wait to go beyond this I felt a
number of coaching businesses scale to
eight figures that's over 10 million
dollars a year that's over a million
dollars a month but actually building my
own business to that level has been
incredible and it's because of one thing
if you had talked to me four years ago
and listen this podcast is kind of a way
to do that you can go listen back to
some of the previous episodes
when I first started this honestly I
wasn't very confident in my ability to
sell and selling and I and I really was
Jaded by the way that people sell in the
industry funny enough episode number two
I actually break down the same sales
system that I use today but I'm so much
more confident in it because I believe
it is the most ethical way to sell to
people without manipulation without hype
without
lying really I mean let's be honest a
lot of sales and stuff that's out there
is is lying to the customer and it's BS
it's terrible
I'm not going to promote something like
that and and I know that if you're
listening to this podcast you don't want
a system like that at all and so I'm
going to be talking about sales from my
perspective My Philosophy on sales as
well as how to get more sales in your
business we've been doing this a lot
with our high level coaching group and I
want to help you with that as well one
of the first places that I have people
start with sales this book The Way of
the Wolf by Jordan Belfort
straight line selling you might be
saying well Jeremiah I thought you were
talking about ethics
he's not really the poster child for
ethics it's true if you watch the movie
The Way The Wolf of Wall Street
he did not have the most ethical past
but what he teaches about sales is what
I believe to be the most ethical system
when it comes to sales and everything
that I do in my business is the
foundations of this plus what I've
learned over the last 20 years working
in the industry of coaching and online
courses and here's basically the
foundation of it
trust building
the reason anybody spends money with you
is they trust you
they trust that what you say is true
now you could calm people by lying to
them and being really good at lying and
building trust in your lie and
unfortunately whether you're going to do
that or not trust building goes both
ways if you're a person of honesty and
integrity which I hope you are if you're
listening to this podcast because
honestly I don't resonate with people
that aren't you you
owe it to yourself even more to build
trust with people see I see this happen
a lot people who operate with honesty
and integrity don't want to look like
the con man
they don't want to look like
the manipulator they don't want to look
like the person who is Sleazy and slimy
and so they're so worried about managing
appearances managing the mask they put
over their face managing their
reputation and what everybody thinks
about them
and then they don't sell because they're
afraid of looking like the dude who's
doing it unethically
I was this way when I first started in
my business I was not wanting to look
like those con artist coaches that are
out there that you know they just they
promise results and don't actually
deliver and I was concerned that people
would think that in fact I would get
accused of it in my advertisements
people would be like you know there's no
way this works blah blah blah and it
would actually really bother me and so
I'm like how can I make people not think
this about me how can the truth is this
foreign
there's nothing that you can do to make
people
not think those things of you there's
always going to be a segment of people
that are haters there's always going to
be a segment of people that do not like
you
that's why the system that we teach is
to qualify people around
who is the best buyer to make sure that
you have the right people that you're
talking to okay
and we're not going to use hype we're
not going to use manipulation but you do
need to use boldness
and courage and belief
if you have a system that can help
people
I believe and I'm just going to say this
right here this is for those that are in
my coaching program you know this to be
true
for those that are not what I'm about to
say might sound like hype
because you're not in the program
we have the best coaching program to
help you get more clients
in the industry
to help you create virtual events to get
more leads on your email list to get
more coaching clients and every single
person who joins our program says that
and they're getting results and so I
actually
with that being true
owe it to myself and the world to let as
many people know about my program as
possible whether they believe it's true
or not whether they think I'm Legit or
not that's none of my business
that's none of my concerns see here's
the problem when we're concerned about
how we look to others
when we're concerned about
sounding right
doing the right thing I'm not hear me
out
I'm going to say this
I'm not condoning that you defraud
people when I say to stop worrying about
doing the right thing I'm not condoning
you actually go out there and do the
wrong thing but it's the mental concern
about making sure that everything is
just so
with no deviation from how they should
be and best practices and and this is
the the right only right way to do it
the truth is there's no right or really
wrong way of doing business there's so
many different ways of doing business
and that's why most people fail at
business is because they're looking for
the right one perfect way to do it when
it doesn't exist the only thing that has
actually right is to launch imperfectly
to experiment to be willing to take a
risk and it not turn out how you want it
to to be okay with
launching something out there and not
returning how you expected it
that my friends is actually the most and
only right way to build a business yet
most people are living in the fantasy
land that they're going to finally find
someday the one perfect method to do
everything and then it's gonna finally
produce results for them doesn't exist
doesn't exist on Planet Earth at all
okay so once you realize that
you can go out there and actually build
a business that makes money that's
that's the shocking part of it it's like
Excalibur sword you ever heard the story
of of The Sword and the stone is that
everybody thought it would take strength
to pull it out when the very thing that
would pull the sword out of the stone
was not a stronger man
and that's how I've always likened
business there's usually contrarian
principles the thing that most people
think is the most right thing to do in
business often is not
often is not
maybe you're somebody right now and
you're watching this and you're like man
Jeremiah I cringe when I watch webinars
and people sell and I just like it's so
inauthentic and gross and disgusting I
don't want to be one of those gross and
disgusting ew icky yucky people
ah
well guess what
you might need to challenge that belief
about sales and about sales people
and about what it means to sell
and what it means to bring an
opportunity to people that's going to
help them
if you've been trying to build a
business and you've not made any sales
because you cringe at the idea of
selling
that has more to do with your mindset
and your belief system than anything
else is because somewhere inside
there's a belief that you have that it's
bad and wrong to do the things that
sales people do
and so you're looking for some Mickey
Mouse Disneyland perfect version of of
how to make sales without doing the the
thing that makes you feel uncomfortable
and this is what I I see happen more
often than not
in business
I was one of those people I was so
uncomfortable to do the things that it
takes to sell
because I had these thoughts in my head
invalidating me telling me that I wasn't
good enough telling me that I sounded
like a scam artist that I sounded like
somebody that people couldn't trust that
I was that I wasn't somebody that people
should do business with whatever these
crappy ideas that we come up with our
head and that that that that that our
our brain convinces Us of for why we
can't boldly and courageously ask people
to buy from us what we sell
the worst of all is TR is trying to not
sound like a salesperson
is trying to not look like somebody one
of those people out there that does like
like
I see this
uh I'm not going to be like one of those
people out there who sell like a slimy
slime ball
and yet they're broke
they're not making money
I meet them every single day
and they call me arrogant funny
when their level of arrogance will not
even allow them
to do what is effective
to bring in sales and again I'm not
asking you to to do anything
that you're that is hypey that is
manipulative that is slimy that is
sleazy
but I want you to challenge the
judgments that you've made towards other
sales people
towards people
who sell online
how you've seen yourself as better than
them and them below you and how you
would never do the things that they do
to get sales
see most of the in fact over 50 percent
of the coaches that I meet
have this stigma about sales and about
selling and about sales people
and these standards that they've built
up in their mind of of well I will never
cross that line to make money
[Music]
I will never cross that line to look or
sound or behave that way
like those disgusting people
and that's that's actually more than 50
of the coaches that I meet it's really
it's sad because
they don't know
that first off you don't listen there's
some slimy sales people out there
but you might have to do
some of the things that you judged as
wrong and are uncomfortable for you to
start to bring in sales into your
business and you might need to work on
what are the beliefs between your two
ears that tell you
that those actions are wrong
that those actions are disgusting
really challenged I mean I mean really
start to sit with that
and if you watch me in my selling I
asked my wife this question today I said
honey did do you
think that I'm over hypey and
manipulative in my salesperson she's
like absolutely not she's like I tell
you if you were
okay great for those of you that have
ever watched me do a virtual event if
you're part of my accelerator you can
see me do this I'm not hypey or
manipulative in how I sell
but I am bold and I am courageous and I
have a level of self-belief that is
unshakable
because I know that I know that I know
that what I offer people
works and it changes lives
and if I had even a shred of doubt in
that even a tiny Inkling of not
believing that we wouldn't make money in
our business
the level of income that you make is
directly related to the level of
self-esteem that you have
and believing in yourself and then
showing up and demonstrating that energy
to people
and not being concerned about what
anybody thinks about you not being
concerned about how you look or how you
sound to anybody I want to challenge you
to do that
I want to challenge you to show up
with boldness and confidence
imagine that you were me
when you go to sell
how would I sell your product how would
I sell your program
think about that
and be bolder and if maybe you're like
listen I have no belief in myself then
you might need to work on what's up here
that is telling you that you're not good
enough for people to buy from that your
value is lesser than what people should
purchase from that people shouldn't have
the level of respect for you or your
time to buy from you that that people
should just use you and abuse you for
your time because that's what they've
always done your whole life you see does
that make you feel good because if it
does you might need to challenge where
people using you to make you feel good
came from
you might need to challenge where you
came up with the belief
that people taking advantage of you
means
that you have worth
I had that belief for a long time
that my worth was directly proportionate
to the level that people take advantage
of me
I didn't make any money with that
I didn't think I was worthy of people
spending money with me
I don't think my time was valuable
I didn't think my time was worth what I
was asking
now
my time is actually worth way more than
I'm asking
and I need to start asking more for it
and I will be in the next two to three
months I have a strategy right now
to 325x the money that's coming in in
our business
and I will be charging a heck of a lot
more for everything
and so should you
you should raise your prices
you should start charging more
not less
start respecting yourself more see the
reason why we don't charge enough is
because we don't have a level of respect
for ourselves and so what we do is we
open up our boundary and we allow
anybody to get a piece of us for nothing
when you can learn to start respecting
yourself more
and stop giving
so much of yourself to everybody for
free to find validation to be liked by
people
for people to tell you that you are
worthy of love and acceptance
by how much they use and abuse you and
take advantage of you and you actually
start charging money for what you do and
you actually start asking people and say
and when people are saying man can I get
a discount you say no I'm sorry I don't
offer discounts man can I barter with
you for that no I don't barter for
anything man you're a jerk for not
partying a man you're an for not
for charging money for that you're not
worth that I've had people come at me
and tell me that
now I got a choice to make am I going to
believe them
or am I going to believe me that my
worth is so far above and beyond what
anybody tries to force into my head when
anybody else tells me that I'm worth I
got people all day long tell me that I'm
worthless in my direct mess I got
somebody so many people when I raise my
prices to thirty thousand dollars for
one-on-one coaching ripping me a new one
as to what a horrible human being I am
for charging that much
great let them not my problem
not my concern
and it's not yours either what other
people think of you is not any of your
concern
it's not any of your worry
it's not anything that you should be
concerned about
focus on
the people who are going to get the most
value out of your programs
and then focus on who is actually buying
from you and spending the most amount of
money with you and then focus on how can
I deliver more results to those people
and that will change your life that will
change your business
that will change how you look at
yourself and the world and you'll stop
giving yourself away to people
for cheap
for nothing
and you'll start actually asking
people to pay your worth
there's nothing Noble in giving yourself
away to people I'm sorry I'm going to
say that and I may offend some people
there is nothing Noble in giving all of
you away to people for free
you can have more impact and help more
people by charging what you're worth
because then you can start to advertise
and you can start to hire people and you
can actually start to work less and be
more effective your content will
actually get better
when you're not the one doing all the
work in your business this solopreneur
dream isn't really a dream once you're
working 40 to 60 hours a week
it's time for you to start to charge
more make more money and ask people to
pay you what you're worth
so that you can have the life that you
actually want
you know I'm so saddened by there's so
many people
constantly there's people
they've listened to my podcast for five
years and still
cannot seem to get what I have just
talked about for 20 minutes
just I just can't get it I just can't
get it
it's just escapes them
foreign
[Music]
their priorities are somewhere else
they refuse to sell to people they
refuse to ask people to pay them money
because they are so concerned about
looking like a scammer
looking like a hype Master looking like
a con artist
looking like one of those people
that they literally won't even launch an
offer won't put themselves out there
won't ask anybody to buy from them and
and the saddest one is when I hear
people say because I want to impact
people more
your impact is not
working that way
start asking for the sale
learn to get better at selling we have
courses and mentoring where we help you
in my in my coaching program to help you
get better at selling we have one of the
best sales courses that exists out there
specifically for people that struggle to
believe in themselves with selling what
I've done is I've taken some of the best
sales courses and I do I do recommend
you read this book I recommend you grab
it I recommend you get the audiobook
and and start
to become better at selling the only way
that you can actually make money in a
coaching business is to sell that's it
like people give you money for your
coaching
and you have to actually like
build trust with them and lead them to
buy from you
you actually have to make a connection
with a person that needs what you offer
and sell to them
but if you're if if your brain is
blocking you
and you believe it's wrong to sell to
people
you won't make any money
because you won't do the wrong thing
that you believe is the most wrong thing
that I must always avoid that's what
your brain will tell you red flag red
flag danger danger avoid this never sell
never ask anybody to buy from you always
give away and if that's what your brain
is flashing lights doing you might need
to reprogram that part of your brain
reprogramming your brain isn't a bad
thing we're always constantly
reprogramming our brain when you listen
to a podcast like this when you go
through coaching you are reprogramming
certain parts of your brain that are not
working towards your goals if you are
physically incapable of selling to
people that is an area of your life that
is not serving you for your goals it's
just not if you have a goal to make a
half a million dollars you've been
trying for 20 years but you won't sell
and your brain tells you don't sell it's
bad to sell it's bad it's wrong it's
uncomfortable people don't like it I'm
gonna look bad people are going to think
bad things about me and you operate from
that framework
don't you won't make enough money for
the next 20 years
until you reprogram
that thing
inside of you that tells you that it's
wrong and you get to the root and you
identify where did I come up with this
belief that I should never do the very
thing that's going to make me money
where did I come up with the belief that
it's wrong
to ask people to buy from me something
and challenge that belief
and challenge
why
you won't build your business no no no
you're like but Jeremiah I'm building my
business and building my business if
you're not asking for the sale you're
not building anything
you're just wasting time on a
time-consuming hobby
and that's the saddest thing that I see
people do they get leads on their email
list and then they don't even sell them
because they're afraid of bugging people
they're afraid of annoying people
they're afraid of pissing people off
they're afraid of people unsubscribing
that's the funniest one
well I spent so much on those leads I
don't want to lose them
50 of the leads that subscribe to all of
our email lists unsubscribe and I ask
them to because they're not even people
that are going to get value from what we
offer anyways they're just what we call
Lucky Lou's and in one ear out the next
they're not gonna pay attention to
anything that we actually have to say
but when you can
start to work on
what is that thing inside of you that's
telling you I can't sell
I can't sell I'm too afraid to ask for
the sale I'm too afraid to ask people to
buy for me see that's the thing if
you're afraid of a runaway Facebook ads
bill
if you're afraid of losing all this
money
I guess I get it if you're incapable of
asking for the sale yeah you probably
will lose money
because you're never going to make
enough money to pay back everything else
until you start behaving differently
until you work on what is that thing
between your two ears that is telling
you it is wrong
to sell
and you start to realize it's actually
very right and very good and very
ethical to ask people to buy from you
and to be paid well and to be able to
leverage your pay to grow a business to
hire people to run advertisements to
reach more people
you got two choices to make are we going
to keep operating in the framework of
how you've lived your life for the last
20 30 40 years
are you going to start to do something
differently that might feel
uncomfortable at first
that might not feel natural to you
but that will get you
so much closer to that goal that you
have
to reach your goals you're gonna have to
do some uncomfortable things and I'm not
asking you to do anything immoral or
unethical
I'm not
but it will feel that way sometimes in
your brain it will feel almost as if
you're doing something immoral or
unethical let me explain that
like you will your physiology
your feelings inside of you your body
might get the same tension as if you're
about to do something that you know you
shouldn't even though it's actually a
very good thing to ask people to buy
from you that's what it felt like to me
I was so afraid
to ask people to buy my coaching program
I was so afraid of how people would
judge it and we've gotten nothing but
rave reviews from people and yet I was
still terrified even six months ago when
we launched it
because I didn't think I was good enough
and it's only been recently that I've
started to believe you know what
everybody else is telling me this this
isn't just a one-time fluke I have
literally had people tell me I have gone
through and I'm not going to name names
but they did name some names
the top coaching programs on the planet
and they're like Jeremiah yours is a
hundred times better than theirs
it's humbling it really is
it really is
because I didn't think I was that that
good
at the same time I've operated out of
spirit of excellence and I've delivered
the best training
this podcast
is a labor of love we don't have
hundreds of subscribers and yet every
week I've stayed faithful to the
episodes delivering the highest quality
content
and I've seen the effects of it we've
had people's lives are changed making
millions of dollars using what we teach
but I know that I can do more and I know
that I can reach more people and I know
that if every coach out there gets this
and understands this and understands my
message and understands how to sell
better and works on What's between their
two ears that is stopping them
the world will change and the world will
be made a better place because of it
listen if you're a coach and you're
somebody that knows other coaches that
are out there please share this episode
with them if they struggle to sell
please share this with other people
consider getting on the waiting list for
our grow your our client growth
accelerator our group coaching program
and start selling with boldness
and courage
and start believing that what you offer
to people is incredible
it'll change your life when you start
seeing what you offer as absolutely
incredible stop thinking about it as
it's okay
it's okay see I had to start realizing
that our program is absolutely
incredible
is it perfect no nothing's perfect
nothing I do is perfect so one of my
number one things I tell people is you
got to kill perfectionism
I posted this on my social media today
I'm saddened by people who never go
after their dreams out of a spirit of
Excellence because a spirit of
excellence and perfectionism
kills more dreams than mistakes ever
will
and you have to kill the desire to do
everything perfect
the right thing is almost always never
the perfect thing that we have in our
mind
do the imperfect less perfect thing
today instead of waiting for Perfection
to arrive tomorrow in your life in your
business it'll change everything for you
and when it comes to selling listen
you're not going to be perfect you're
probably going to flub it up the first
couple of times and that's okay
but give it your best and work on what's
going on up here
to operate out of Courage boldness
and the highest level of self-belief
and you'll make more money than you ever
imagined
and help way more people in the process
grow your life everybody thanks for
listening we'll talk soon